<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Images &amp; Words</title>
    <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Images &amp; Words</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:20:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>2021 05 27</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 23:28:57 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thursday, May 27, 11:41 AM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting interview and idea regarding mindsets (scout vs soldier). Basic premise seems to be that the soldier mindset is obsessed with changing or attacking or defending beliefs and situations (assumed to be for the better),  where as the scout mindset is centered around consciously trying to build a better &amp;ldquo;map&amp;rdquo; or with seeing things as they are instead of attacking or defending. I think I will buy her book &amp;ldquo;The Scout Mindset: Why Some People See Things Clearly and Others Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo;  and give it a read, premise sounds interesting. Even though I grew up idolizing the solider, I&amp;rsquo;m at a place where I think the explorer might be the cooler one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://noahpinion.substack.com/p/interview-julia-galef&#34;&gt;https://noahpinion.substack.com/p/interview-julia-galef&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thursday, May 27, 10:39 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Friends : Reunion episode was pretty much everything I expected it to be (in a good way). It felt like a relatively chill hour spend in the company of old college friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thursday, May 27, 10:53 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insightful conversation on ways to combat misinformation and things to look out for when a casual observation makes it seem like the science has not fully settled on a given topic(if may never do in totality). Also touches on the importance of trusting the source of a particular factoid and ways to critically evaluate information from seeming credible sources (e.g is this scientist writing an op-ed because his peers don&amp;rsquo;t take him seriously ?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nautil.us/issue/100/outsiders/why-misinformation-is-about-who-you-trust-not-what-you-think-rp?utm_source=RSS_Feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=RSS&amp;amp;utm_campaign=RSS_Syndication&#34;&gt;http://nautil.us/issue/100/outsiders/why-misinformation-is-about-who-you-trust-not-what-you-think-rp?utm_source=RSS_Feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=RSS&amp;amp;utm_campaign=RSS_Syndication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>2021 05 26</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:56:10 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday, May 26, 7:14 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s Astrazeneca opt-in rollout across Malaysia seemed like it was a crap fest. I think there were fundamental mistakes made in how the entire booking portal was architected. The form design itself was decent enough (except for Google&amp;rsquo;s captcha that has a very English speaker/American bias).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly, there was no reason to make this so complicated, I wish they had just made the opt-in a profile level setting in mysejahtera and should have just used that data to prioritize in the same old fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday, May 26, 8:58 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lot of vaccine hesitation ongoing within the main vaccination stream(which is targeting senior citizens) in Malaysia. I wonder how much of it is fueled by whatsapp and facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2021/05/693310/9009-people-perak-fail-turn-their-vaccination&#34;&gt;https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2021/05/693310/9009-people-perak-fail-turn-their-vaccination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday, May 26, 8:59 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In depth look at the challenges faced in the USA with regards to accurately compiling statistics around reporting testing and death related metrics during the early days of the COVID-19 pandemic, and the impact it had on America&amp;rsquo;s spectacular failure to get a grip on the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/05/pandemic-data-america-messy/618987/?utm_source=feed&#34;&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/05/pandemic-data-america-messy/618987/?utm_source=feed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday, May 26, 9:04 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learned about the Penrose hypothesis, which postulates an inversely proportional relationship between asylum population and prison population (especially in the United States). I guess I never thought about the fact that not institutionalizing someone with severe mental health challenges almost predictably results in the same individuals getting caught up in the criminal justice system due to (arguably) preventable violent crimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/05/truth-about-deinstitutionalization/618986/?utm_source=feed&#34;&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/05/truth-about-deinstitutionalization/618986/?utm_source=feed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>2021 05 25</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday, May 25, 8:46 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting article that talks about how Israel, by having the perfect band-aid/painkiller has stopped prioritizing solving the real problem that&amp;rsquo;s driving the need for the band-aid/painkiller in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2021/05/iron-dome-israel-netanyahu-hamas/618973/?utm_source=feed&#34;&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2021/05/iron-dome-israel-netanyahu-hamas/618973/?utm_source=feed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday, May 25, 9:48 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Argument that there is a cover-up of sorts happening about the effectiveness of Ivermectic as a treatment for COVID-19. What makes me skeptical is that all reports that support the drug cite India as a testing ground, but as far as I can tell, only one or two states have started trying it out.  I&amp;rsquo;m yet to see any evidence that this has resulted in a massive reduction in death rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the pro-Ivermectin articles point to reduction in cases, which I think is better attributed to stringent lockdown protocols in place rather than any wonder drug&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2021/05/i-dont-know-of-a-bigger-story-in-the-world-right-now-than-ivermectin-ny-times-best-selling-author.html?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+nakedcapitalism+%28naked+capitalism%29&#34;&gt;https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2021/05/i-dont-know-of-a-bigger-story-in-the-world-right-now-than-ivermectin-ny-times-best-selling-author.html?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+nakedcapitalism+%28naked+capitalism%29&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday, May 25, 9:52 PM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh no. They are going to turn Portal into a movie. Still on the fence about this (although I hope they bring in J K Simmons as Cave Johnson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theverge.com/2021/5/24/22452272/jj-abrams-portal-movie-valve-half-life-2013-script-production&#34;&gt;https://www.theverge.com/2021/5/24/22452272/jj-abrams-portal-movie-valve-half-life-2013-script-production&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Book Recap : Talking to Strangers</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 01:02:20 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/talking-to-strangers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Talking to Strangers&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the second Malcolm Gladwell book I&amp;rsquo;ve read so far. I read &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/3228917-outliers&#34;&gt;Outliers&lt;/a&gt; nearly a decade ago and thought that, while it certainly was an interesting read, it didn&amp;rsquo;t personally contain any ground-breaking insight as far as I was concerned. At the risk of sounding reductionist, I thought the conclusion that success, while often (mis)attributed to talent is always backed up by time invested by the person involved, was sort of a given.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Talking to Strangers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; much more enjoyable and insightful. The central thesis of this book is that generally, us .. human beings, are spectacularly and demonstrably bad at sizing up and gauging the true intention of strangers we interact with on a day to day basis. This major blind spot affects us all equally regardless of whether we&amp;rsquo;re corporate workers, cops, CIA agents, FBI agents, Prime Ministers, judges&amp;hellip;the list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gladwell&amp;rsquo;s central thesis builds around 3 relatively straight forward concepts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For mostly evolutionary and society building reasons humans almost always assume that the person on the other side of the conversation is being truthful (originally proposed by a psychology study titled &lt;strong&gt;Truth Default Theory&lt;/strong&gt; by &lt;em&gt;Timothy Levine&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We erroneously assume that true representations of people&amp;rsquo;s intentions are &amp;ldquo;readable&amp;rdquo; from their facial expressions and body language. Gladwell cites a wide variety of historical examples and scientific studies that help illustrate just how bad we are at reading other people. He also cites the popularity of the TV show &lt;em&gt;Friends&lt;/em&gt; as a result of all characters being unambiguously and truthfully expressive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The idea of &amp;ldquo;coupling&amp;rdquo; which postulates that people&amp;rsquo;s behaviors(even in extreme cases like suicide) is closely linked with verify specific circumstances and conditions that are external to them rather than something intrinsic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last one sounded a bit too obvious to me, but I was surprised to read the examples he cited, like how suicide rate among women in the UK plummeted after UK switched to natural gas instead of coal-derived Carbon Monoxide laced cooking gas which apparently was an oft deployed suicide tool in the UK (victims include the likes of Slyvia Plath).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book also took some informative detours to illustrate wider implications of our inability to accurately read strangers, including&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why &amp;ldquo;enhanced interrogation techniques&amp;rdquo; (fancy politically sterile phrase for torture) don&amp;rsquo;t work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How judges who routinely make &amp;ldquo;gut feel&amp;rdquo; calls about defendants based on their appearance before setting bail end up misreading intentions/guilt/remorse. In fact a study out of Harvard ended up proving that a pre-trained computer program can be demonstrably more accurate at setting bail terms than human judges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why the CIA took too long to detect Castro&amp;rsquo;s spies among its ranks for years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep dives into why authorities in places like Penn State University sat on allegations of sexual misconduct against its staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, I thought &amp;ldquo;Talking to Strangers&amp;rdquo; made for some insightful Sunday pop-science reading and I shall forever label people&amp;rsquo;s claims to be able to &amp;ldquo;read&amp;rdquo; other people&amp;rsquo;s intentions from behavioral ticks and quirks as &amp;ldquo;bullshit&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Book Recap : Samsung Rising</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:31:11 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/samsung-rising.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Samsung Rising&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding out more about the origin stories of successful companies is always an informative and entertaining endeavor. For me that list so far includes ..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/339584.Game_Over_Press_Start_to_Continue&#34;&gt;Game Over, Press Start to Continue&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Nintendo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/798635.iWoz&#34;&gt;iWoz: Computer Geek to Cult Icon: How I Invented the Personal Computer, Co-Founded Apple, and Had Fun Doing It&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Apple&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/222146.Masters_of_Doom&#34;&gt;Masters of Doom&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;id Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/7049142-showstopper-the-breakneck-race-to-create-windows-nt-and-the-next-genera&#34;&gt;Showstopper! the Breakneck Race to Create Windows NT and the Next Generation at Microsoft&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest addition to the above list is &lt;strong&gt;Samsung Rising&lt;/strong&gt; by &lt;em&gt;Geoffrey Cain&lt;/em&gt; which chronicles Samsung&amp;rsquo;s rise from an agricultural company to something more akin to The Umbrella Corporation. Samsung&amp;rsquo;s story in broad strokes is closely associated with the Republic of Korea which is semi-playfully often referred to as the Republic of Samsung. This also results in this book serving as a crash course into the economic rise of the South Korea as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author uses a behind the scenes look into the explosive(literally) train wreck that was the Galaxy Note 7 to bookend the broader narrative of Samsung&amp;rsquo;s meteoric rise. Following is a list of key takeaways that I compiled from my notes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tale-of-2-lees&#34;&gt;Tale of 2 Lee&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lee Byung Chul era (founding chairman)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bulk of Samsung&amp;rsquo;s financial success can be attributed to the extremely shrewd long game played by its founding Chairman Lee Byung-chul&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His decision to invest in NAND flash storage and other corner stones of electronics manufacturing ensured that even if Samsung&amp;rsquo;s own products failed they will still have enough cash flow presence from other sources. He met with and even got along well with the pre-NEXT era Steve Jobs which I guess demonstrates the extent of his long game&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He shaped the formative culture of Samsung (even to the extent of personally sitting in approximately 100,000 interviews) because he believed in an overly cautious approach to hiring. He also famously prized lifetime loyalty. Over his tenure this resulted in Samsung being filled with lifetime &amp;ldquo;generalists&amp;rdquo; colloquially known as &amp;ldquo;Samsung Men&amp;rdquo; who were understandably valued in the South Korean dating scene.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He admired the Japanese work ethic, resilience and corporate practices and encouraged his employees to watch and learn from the Japanese instead of being fearful of their former colonizer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He successfully tapped into the South Korean spirit of patriotism and managed to convert people&amp;rsquo;s need to be part of something greater than their own self into unwavering loyalty to the Republic of Samsung.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lee Kun Hee era&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primarily credited with Samsung&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of operational excellence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Famously delivered a 3 day diatribe at a Samsung conference in Frankfurt chastising Samsung&amp;rsquo;s shoddy manufacturing and other existential problems. He famously ordered his troops to &amp;ldquo;Change everything except your wife and children&amp;rdquo;. Samsung&amp;rsquo;s internal historians now label his philosophy &amp;ldquo;perpetual crisis&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He spearheaded a top-down focus on quality control, reduction of waste and healthy paranoia to along with his sense of &lt;em&gt;perpetual crisis&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Took inspiration from the Japanese management practice of &amp;ldquo;gaiatsu&amp;rdquo; and started roping in external agents (from Europe and the US) as an outside force to bring in sweeping change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;miscellaneous-factoids&#34;&gt;Miscellaneous factoids&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was surprised by how readily Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Japanese competitors also acted like faithful teachers who offered wisdom, guidance and straight talk to Samsung&amp;rsquo;s leadership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was also unaware of the role good old American branding and marketing capabilities played in building the Samsung brand as it is known today (all the way from buying out prime spots on Times Square to getting Ellen to take that record breaking selfie while she was hosting the Oscars).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I always thought Samsung ended up incidentally or accidentally competing with Apple and boy was I wrong. They consciously and intentionally decided to go after Apple&amp;rsquo;s share of the smartphone pie in a very David vs Goliath way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mad props to Samsung engineers who apparently when granted an &amp;ldquo;eyes only&amp;rdquo; visit to Micron&amp;rsquo;s factories in the US, memorized diagrams they saw and recreated them from memory after returning to their hotel rooms at night. Reminded me of a story of Mozart doing something similar in his childhood making him one of the earlier known music pirates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Galaxy&amp;rdquo; range of smartphones (I myself am on my 3rd Galaxy phone) was named after a brand of wine Samsung executives came across in California.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Korean art of &amp;ldquo;nunchi&amp;rdquo; which sort of means the &amp;ldquo;art of gauging others&amp;rsquo; moods&amp;rdquo; and was an essential skill to have if one wanted to survive Samsung&amp;rsquo;s corporate culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;closing-thoughts&#34;&gt;Closing thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Samsung Rising&lt;/em&gt; is a relatively straightforward read that delivered pretty much what I expected from the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally think the the whole &amp;ldquo;exploding Galaxy Note 7&amp;rdquo; saga is always over-interpreted(particularly by the Western press and the author is no exception here) through the whole &amp;ldquo;Asian&amp;rdquo; cultural lens while its far more likely to be a &amp;ldquo;big company&amp;rdquo; problem than a &amp;ldquo;Korean&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Asian&amp;rdquo; problem. You can even see this in other product disasters like the ongoing 737 Max saga at Boeing (a traditionally American company).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt like it lost a bit of steam midway, especially when Samsung&amp;rsquo;s upper echelons got mired in political scandals that rocked South Korea. While the chain of events that transpired does make an entertaining political read, it came across as a distraction from what I perceived to be the book&amp;rsquo;s central thesis of attempting to unpack how an agricultural manufacturer from an impoverished war torn country turned itself(and the country) around to be one of the most valuable technology conglomerates of the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 14:17:12 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/ -&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have not set-up a new blog in more than a decade and I haven’t written a public blog post in more than 5 years. I can finally cross a dangling item in my to do list and I hope I can be disciplined enough to write regularly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Years and years of consuming text and never producing any does not seem right.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:20:36 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/ -&lt;p&gt;Now what or who am I? As soon as I started writing this page the following exchange from the first Avengers film played back in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Steve Rogers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; : Big man in a suit of armour. Take that off and what are you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tony Stark&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; : Billionaire, Genius, Playboy, Philanthropist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gotta admire the confidence of someone who can rattle off a list of on-point adjectives to answer what’s essentially the question the “about” page of a blog template asks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I do not qualify for any of the above adjectives Mr Homo Ferrum used there. Although I do know that if I could be any Avenger, I’d choose to be Cap.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss> 