<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Images &amp; Words</title>
    <link>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Images &amp; Words</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:20:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Book Recap : Samsung Rising</title>
        <link>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:31:11 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/ -&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/samsung-rising.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Samsung Rising&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding out more about the origin stories of successful companies is always an informative and entertaining endeavor. For me that list so far includes ..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/339584.Game_Over_Press_Start_to_Continue&#34;&gt;Game Over, Press Start to Continue&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Nintendo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/798635.iWoz&#34;&gt;iWoz: Computer Geek to Cult Icon: How I Invented the Personal Computer, Co-Founded Apple, and Had Fun Doing It&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Apple&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/222146.Masters_of_Doom&#34;&gt;Masters of Doom&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;id Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/7049142-showstopper-the-breakneck-race-to-create-windows-nt-and-the-next-genera&#34;&gt;Showstopper! the Breakneck Race to Create Windows NT and the Next Generation at Microsoft&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest addition to the above list is &lt;strong&gt;Samsung Rising&lt;/strong&gt; by &lt;em&gt;Geoffrey Cain&lt;/em&gt; which chronicles Samsung&amp;rsquo;s rise from an agricultural company to something more akin to The Umbrella Corporation. Samsung&amp;rsquo;s story in broad strokes is closely associated with the Republic of Korea which is semi-playfully often referred to as the Republic of Samsung. This also results in this book serving as a crash course into the economic rise of the South Korea as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author uses a behind the scenes look into the explosive(literally) train wreck that was the Galaxy Note 7 to bookend the broader narrative of Samsung&amp;rsquo;s meteoric rise. Following is a list of key takeaways that I compiled from my notes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tale-of-2-lees&#34;&gt;Tale of 2 Lee&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lee Byung Chul era (founding chairman)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bulk of Samsung&amp;rsquo;s financial success can be attributed to the extremely shrewd long game played by its founding Chairman Lee Byung-chul&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His decision to invest in NAND flash storage and other corner stones of electronics manufacturing ensured that even if Samsung&amp;rsquo;s own products failed they will still have enough cash flow presence from other sources. He met with and even got along well with the pre-NEXT era Steve Jobs which I guess demonstrates the extent of his long game&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He shaped the formative culture of Samsung (even to the extent of personally sitting in approximately 100,000 interviews) because he believed in an overly cautious approach to hiring. He also famously prized lifetime loyalty. Over his tenure this resulted in Samsung being filled with lifetime &amp;ldquo;generalists&amp;rdquo; colloquially known as &amp;ldquo;Samsung Men&amp;rdquo; who were understandably valued in the South Korean dating scene.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He admired the Japanese work ethic, resilience and corporate practices and encouraged his employees to watch and learn from the Japanese instead of being fearful of their former colonizer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He successfully tapped into the South Korean spirit of patriotism and managed to convert people&amp;rsquo;s need to be part of something greater than their own self into unwavering loyalty to the Republic of Samsung.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lee Kun Hee era&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primarily credited with Samsung&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of operational excellence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Famously delivered a 3 day diatribe at a Samsung conference in Frankfurt chastising Samsung&amp;rsquo;s shoddy manufacturing and other existential problems. He famously ordered his troops to &amp;ldquo;Change everything except your wife and children&amp;rdquo;. Samsung&amp;rsquo;s internal historians now label his philosophy &amp;ldquo;perpetual crisis&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He spearheaded a top-down focus on quality control, reduction of waste and healthy paranoia to along with his sense of &lt;em&gt;perpetual crisis&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Took inspiration from the Japanese management practice of &amp;ldquo;gaiatsu&amp;rdquo; and started roping in external agents (from Europe and the US) as an outside force to bring in sweeping change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;miscellaneous-factoids&#34;&gt;Miscellaneous factoids&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was surprised by how readily Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Japanese competitors also acted like faithful teachers who offered wisdom, guidance and straight talk to Samsung&amp;rsquo;s leadership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was also unaware of the role good old American branding and marketing capabilities played in building the Samsung brand as it is known today (all the way from buying out prime spots on Times Square to getting Ellen to take that record breaking selfie while she was hosting the Oscars).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I always thought Samsung ended up incidentally or accidentally competing with Apple and boy was I wrong. They consciously and intentionally decided to go after Apple&amp;rsquo;s share of the smartphone pie in a very David vs Goliath way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mad props to Samsung engineers who apparently when granted an &amp;ldquo;eyes only&amp;rdquo; visit to Micron&amp;rsquo;s factories in the US, memorized diagrams they saw and recreated them from memory after returning to their hotel rooms at night. Reminded me of a story of Mozart doing something similar in his childhood making him one of the earlier known music pirates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Galaxy&amp;rdquo; range of smartphones (I myself am on my 3rd Galaxy phone) was named after a brand of wine Samsung executives came across in California.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Korean art of &amp;ldquo;nunchi&amp;rdquo; which sort of means the &amp;ldquo;art of gauging others&amp;rsquo; moods&amp;rdquo; and was an essential skill to have if one wanted to survive Samsung&amp;rsquo;s corporate culture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;closing-thoughts&#34;&gt;Closing thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Samsung Rising&lt;/em&gt; is a relatively straightforward read that delivered pretty much what I expected from the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally think the the whole &amp;ldquo;exploding Galaxy Note 7&amp;rdquo; saga is always over-interpreted(particularly by the Western press and the author is no exception here) through the whole &amp;ldquo;Asian&amp;rdquo; cultural lens while its far more likely to be a &amp;ldquo;big company&amp;rdquo; problem than a &amp;ldquo;Korean&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Asian&amp;rdquo; problem. You can even see this in other product disasters like the ongoing 737 Max saga at Boeing (a traditionally American company).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I felt like it lost a bit of steam midway, especially when Samsung&amp;rsquo;s upper echelons got mired in political scandals that rocked South Korea. While the chain of events that transpired does make an entertaining political read, it came across as a distraction from what I perceived to be the book&amp;rsquo;s central thesis of attempting to unpack how an agricultural manufacturer from an impoverished war torn country turned itself(and the country) around to be one of the most valuable technology conglomerates of the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;
- http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <link>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 14:17:12 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/ -&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have not set-up a new blog in more than a decade and I haven’t written a public blog post in more than 5 years. I can finally cross a dangling item in my to do list and I hope I can be disciplined enough to write regularly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Years and years of consuming text and never producing any does not seem right.&lt;/p&gt;
- http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 16:20:36 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/</guid>
        <description>Images &amp; Words http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/ -&lt;p&gt;Now what or who am I? As soon as I started writing this page the following exchange from the first Avengers film played back in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Steve Rogers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; : Big man in a suit of armour. Take that off and what are you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tony Stark&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; : Billionaire, Genius, Playboy, Philanthropist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gotta admire the confidence of someone who can rattle off a list of on-point adjectives to answer what’s essentially the question the “about” page of a blog template asks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I do not qualify for any of the above adjectives Mr Homo Ferrum used there. Although I do know that if I could be any Avenger, I’d choose to be Cap.&lt;/p&gt;
- http://blog.waitsforsleep.net/about/ - </description>
        </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss> 