<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Images &amp; Words</title>
    <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Images &amp; Words</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 01:02:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Recap : Talking to Strangers</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 01:02:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</guid>
      <description>This is the second Malcolm Gladwell book I&amp;rsquo;ve read so far. I read Outliers nearly a decade ago and thought that, while it certainly was an interesting read, it didn&amp;rsquo;t personally contain any ground-breaking insight as far as I was concerned. At the risk of sounding reductionist, I thought the conclusion that success, while often (mis)attributed to talent is always backed up by time invested by the person involved, was sort of a given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Recap : Samsung Rising</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:31:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</guid>
      <description>Finding out more about the origin stories of successful companies is always an informative and entertaining endeavor. For me that list so far includes ..
 Game Over, Press Start to Continue about Nintendo iWoz: Computer Geek to Cult Icon: How I Invented the Personal Computer, Co-Founded Apple, and Had Fun Doing It about Apple Masters of Doom about id Software Showstopper! the Breakneck Race to Create Windows NT and the Next Generation at Microsoft about Microsoft  The latest addition to the above list is Samsung Rising by Geoffrey Cain which chronicles Samsung&amp;rsquo;s rise from an agricultural company to something more akin to The Umbrella Corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>