<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Images &amp; Words</title>
    <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Images &amp; Words</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:44:56 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 06 01</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:44:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-06-01/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, June 1, 10:51 AM
Mildly nostalgia inducing piece about why Wordstar was the perfect word processor for creative writers.
I feel like the argument about the advantages of being a modal editor probably also carries over the the classic text editors like vi(m) or even emacs.
https://www.sfwriter.com/wordstar.htm
 Tuesday, June 1, 10:54 AM
Confirmation bias read on how connections and social circle emphasize memes about certain class of people being more capable than others when in reality good fortune and being at the right place is what&amp;rsquo;s most important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 30</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 11:49:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Sunday, May 30, 3:11 PM
The only fiction I&amp;rsquo;ve read in the past year or two is science fiction (with the exception of an odd Jack Reacher novel). The idea of writing science fiction itself is intriguing and is the source of some fantasizing on my part.
Will probably check out Orson Scott Card&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How to Write Science Fiction and Fantasy&amp;rdquo; as referenced by this essay sometime.
https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JZ9czc5CCX39wsviM/how-to-write-science-fiction-and-fantasy-a-short-summary
 Sunday, May 30, 3:37 PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 29</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:58:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-29/</guid>
      <description>Saturday, May 29, 11:58 AM
Absolutely bonkers report about how flash cards used by US soldiers guarding sensitive spots ended up as an opsec disaster.
I vaguely remember reading reports that fitness bands and running apps(like Runkeeper and Strava) ended up inadvertently revealing unmarked military bases because people noticed public running data that indicated people running in circles in the middle of the desert where official maps say there is nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 28</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 02:19:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-28/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 28, 1:02 AM
Write up that chronicles India&amp;rsquo;s slow motion train-wreck with its indigenously developed Covid vaccine which uses the same inactivated virus tech as the Chinese vaccines.
Another related but interesting point I keep encountering when looking into Covid vaccines is that, logically the inactivated vaccines are the ones one would expect to hold up well against variants, as opposed to mRNA/Adenovirus vector based vaccines that are more preoccupied with Covid-19&amp;rsquo;s spike protein than the virus itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 27</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 23:28:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-27/</guid>
      <description>Thursday, May 27, 11:41 AM
Interesting interview and idea regarding mindsets (scout vs soldier). Basic premise seems to be that the soldier mindset is obsessed with changing or attacking or defending beliefs and situations (assumed to be for the better), where as the scout mindset is centered around consciously trying to build a better &amp;ldquo;map&amp;rdquo; or with seeing things as they are instead of attacking or defending. I think I will buy her book &amp;ldquo;The Scout Mindset: Why Some People See Things Clearly and Others Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo; and give it a read, premise sounds interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 26</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:56:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-26/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday, May 26, 7:14 PM
Today&amp;rsquo;s Astrazeneca opt-in rollout across Malaysia seemed like it was a crap fest. I think there were fundamental mistakes made in how the entire booking portal was architected. The form design itself was decent enough (except for Google&amp;rsquo;s captcha that has a very English speaker/American bias).
Honestly, there was no reason to make this so complicated, I wish they had just made the opt-in a profile level setting in mysejahtera and should have just used that data to prioritize in the same old fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 05 25</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/2021-05-25/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, May 25, 8:46 PM
Interesting article that talks about how Israel, by having the perfect band-aid/painkiller has stopped prioritizing solving the real problem that&amp;rsquo;s driving the need for the band-aid/painkiller in the first place.
https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2021/05/iron-dome-israel-netanyahu-hamas/618973/?utm_source=feed
 Tuesday, May 25, 9:48 PM
Argument that there is a cover-up of sorts happening about the effectiveness of Ivermectic as a treatment for COVID-19. What makes me skeptical is that all reports that support the drug cite India as a testing ground, but as far as I can tell, only one or two states have started trying it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Recap : Talking to Strangers</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 01:02:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/talking-to-strangers/</guid>
      <description>This is the second Malcolm Gladwell book I&amp;rsquo;ve read so far. I read Outliers nearly a decade ago and thought that, while it certainly was an interesting read, it didn&amp;rsquo;t personally contain any ground-breaking insight as far as I was concerned. At the risk of sounding reductionist, I thought the conclusion that success, while often (mis)attributed to talent is always backed up by time invested by the person involved, was sort of a given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Recap : Samsung Rising</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:31:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/samsung-rising/</guid>
      <description>Finding out more about the origin stories of successful companies is always an informative and entertaining endeavor. For me that list so far includes ..
 Game Over, Press Start to Continue about Nintendo iWoz: Computer Geek to Cult Icon: How I Invented the Personal Computer, Co-Founded Apple, and Had Fun Doing It about Apple Masters of Doom about id Software Showstopper! the Breakneck Race to Create Windows NT and the Next Generation at Microsoft about Microsoft  The latest addition to the above list is Samsung Rising by Geoffrey Cain which chronicles Samsung&amp;rsquo;s rise from an agricultural company to something more akin to The Umbrella Corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 14:17:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.waitsforsleep.net/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!! Have not set-up a new blog in more than a decade and I haven’t written a public blog post in more than 5 years. I can finally cross a dangling item in my to do list and I hope I can be disciplined enough to write regularly.
Years and years of consuming text and never producing any does not seem right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>